metamorphablog.com 2014-05-16

# Privacy Statement | Metamorpha

****Metamorpha is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most user friendly and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Metamorpha.com Website and governs data collection and usage. By using the Metamorpha.com website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

**Collection of your Personal Information**

Metamorpha.com utilizes the WordPress blogging platform, therefore Metamorpha does not collect data from its users. The collection of personal information passes through WordPress.com and its own online community of bloggers. All questions or concerns of this data collection should be directed to WordPress.com. When applicable, Metamorpha collects email addresses from users who wish to keep updated about the Metamorpha Ministry as a whole or individual authors / bloggers on the Metamorpha.com site. This information is completely confidential, and will not be sold or used for any other purpose other than the expressed purpose made clear when the email was entered.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Metamorpha.com on publically viewable mediums (blog comments, for instance), this information may be collected and used by others. Metamorpha.com does not edit the content of blog conversations, but it can reject comments according to the personal discernment of any of the bloggers. Any information that passes through these mediums is public information, and not protected by Metamorpha.com.

Metamorpha.com encourages you to review the privacy statements of Websites you choose to link to from Metamorpha.com so that you can understand how those Websites collect, use and share your information. Metamorpha.com is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Metamorpha.com Web site.

**Use of your Personal Information**

Metamorpha.com collects and uses personal information freely given by the user to help provide material and keep users updated of new material, that the user has requested. At no point does Metamorpha.com collect, database, or track user data that is not freely given by the user.

Metamorpha.com does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. In addition, Metamorpha.com may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Metamorpha.com, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

The Metamorpha.com Website will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Metamorpha Ministries or the Metamorpha.com site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Metamorpha Ministries; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Metamorpha.com, or the public.

**Use of Cookies**

The Metamorpha.com Website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Metamorpha.com pages, or register with Metamorpha.com site or services, a cookie helps Metamorpha.com to recall your specific information on subsequent visits.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Metamorpha.com services or Websites you visit.

**Changes to this Statement**

Metamorpha.com will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Metamorpha.com encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Metamorpha.com is protecting your information, and how Metamorpha.com is trying to better serve our members.

**Contact Information**

Metamorpha.com welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Metamorpha.com has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Metamorpha.com at [webmaster@metamorpha.com](mailto:webmaster@metamorpha.com). We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
